(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
お着替え中...
Changing clothes...
なななな　ななじゃなくて
Na-na-na-na, it's not 'na'.
にににに　ににじゃなくて
Ni-ni-ni-ni, it's not 'ni'.
ぬぬぬぬ　ぬぬじゃなくて
Nu-nu-nu-nu, it's not 'nu'.
のののの　ののじゃなくて
No-no-no-no, it's not 'no'.
うーーーっ、ね！
Uuuu, ne!
ねねねねねねねね！大爆走
Nenenenenenenene! Dai Bakuso
ねね！よっしゃよっしゃよっしゃよっしゃ！
Ne-ne! Alright, alright, alright, alright!
ホロライブ5期生オレンジ担当桃鈴ねねです
I'm the orange representative of Hololive's 5th Gen, Momosuzu Nene!
異世界から来ましたアイドル志望の新人VTuber
A rookie VTuber from another world aspiring to be an idol!
ま、とにかく明るくいきましょう
Well, anyway, let's keep things bright!
ちょっとくらい緊張したって　すぐすっ飛んで
Even if I'm a little nervous, it'll fly right off,
うわ！って感じで　さぁ！
like 'whoosh!' so, come on!
ババーン！ってやっていこう　諦めの悪さは長所だよね
Let's do it with a bang! My persistence is a strong point, right?
ねねねねねねねねねねねねねねねね！
Nenenenenenenene...!
そんなこともあるけど
Things like that happen, but...
悔しいこともあるけど
...and frustrating things happen too, but...
大丈夫！今日もしっかりおめかしして
It's okay! Today I'll dress up nicely again,
いつかはきっと　スーパーねねち
...and one day, for sure, I'll be Super Nenechi!
ついてきてね
Follow me!
全力プレイ！こそが正解でしょ
Giving it my all! That's the right answer, isn't it?
思い切りやればなんとかなるよ
If you do it wholeheartedly, things will work out somehow!
ボロボロだっていい
It's okay to be in tatters,
転んだっていい
it's okay to fall,
ただ駆け抜けていこうよ
just keep running through!
ねねねね　大爆走！
Nene-ne-ne, Great Rampage!
ねね！よっしゃよっしゃよっしゃよっしゃ！
Ne-ne! Alright, alright, alright, alright!
野菜ジュースと炭酸とお刺身揃えて準備OK
Vegetable juice, carbonated drinks, and sashimi all set, preparation OK!
昼も苦手　夜も苦手
I'm bad with afternoons and bad with nights,
やっぱり睡眠第一だよね
sleep really is priority number one, right?
ねねねねねねねねねねねねねねねね！
Nenenenenenenene...!
たくさんの人に会いたいな
I want to meet lots of people!
チュッチュ　チュッチュ
Chu-chu, chu-chu
大好きのみんなに愛されたい
I want to be loved by everyone I love!
そしたらなれるんだ　ハイパーねねち
Then I can become Hyper Nenechi!
やっちゃってね
Let's do this!
全力プレイ！こそが正解でしょ
Giving it my all! That's the right answer, isn't it?
歌は誰にも負けたくないんだ
I don't want to lose to anyone when it comes to singing!
大きな声で...
With a loud voice...
ちょっとトイレ行ってくるね
I'll be right back, just going to the bathroom.
LET'S GO TIME!
ねね！
Nene!
よしょよしょよしょよしょ！
Yoisho, yoisho, yoisho, yoisho!
ねね！
Nene!
よしょよしょよしょよしょ！
Yoisho, yoisho, yoisho, yoisho!
なななな ななじゃなくて
Na-na-na-na, it's not "Na"
にににに ににじゃなくて
Ni-ni-ni-ni, it's not "Ni"
ぬぬぬぬ ぬぬじゃなくて
Nu-nu-nu-nu, it's not "Nu"
のののの ののじゃなくて
No-no-no-no, it's not "No"
ただいまー！
I'm back!
最後にねねねねねねねねねねねねねねねね
Lastly, Nene-nene-nene-nene-nene-nene-nene-nene!
ねねねねねねねねねねねねねねねね
Nene-nene-nene-nene-nene-nene-nene-nene!
全力これこそ天下無双 思い切りやればなんとかなるさ
This is total power, Peerless. If you give it your all, it'll work out somehow.
今日を待ってたっていい 明日を待ってたっていい 突っ走っていいこうやって
It's fine to wait for today. It's fine to wait for tomorrow. It's fine to just dash forward like this.
ねねねね
Nene, Nene, Nene, Nene.
大爆走！
Great stampede!
それではまたねねー！
Well then, see you later, Nene!
バイバーイ！
Bye-bye!
みんな、こんねねー！
Hello everyone!
改めてまして、ホロライブ5期生オレンジ担当の 桃鈴ねねです。よろしくねー！
Once again, I'm Momosuzu Nene, in charge of orange for Hololive's 5th generation. Nice to meet you!
ちょっと、しんどい。はぁ、はぁ。
I'm... a bit tired. *pant* *pant*
もうさ、曲の間、息堪えるのねね必死なんだ。
Seriously, Nene was desperate to hold her breath during the song.
というわけで、みんな、ねね、3Dになりましたー！
And so, everyone, Nene has finally become 3D!
イェーイ！イェーイ！
Yay! Yay!
みんな今日はハッシュタグ「#桃鈴ねね3D」でいーっぱい呟いて。 Twitter不具合あるみたいなんだけど、そんな中でもねねのことはトレンド入りさせてください。よろしくお願いします！
Everyone, please tweet a lot today with the hashtag "#MomosuzuNene3D". It seems like there's a Twitter glitch, but even so, please make Nene trend. Thank you!
さぁ、今「ねねねねねねねね!大爆走」聴いていただきましたが、どうでしたでしょうか？
So, you just listened to "Nene-nene-nene-nene! Daibakuso". How did you like it?
さぁ、モデルについてなんだけどさ、みんな、ねね見てこれ。クマモデル！イェーイ！
Now, about the model... everyone, look at this. Bear model! Yay!
見て、ガオガオガオガオ！
Look! Roar, roar, roar, roar!
なんとね、クマのバージョンまで作っていただきました。 ありがとうございます！みんなありがとう！みんなありがとう！
Actually, they even made a bear version for me. Thank you very much! Thank you everyone! Thank you everyone!
さぁ、今日はねねはみんなに、普段レッスンしてきた成果を見せるために今ここに立っていますので、どんどん次に進んでいきたいと思います！
Well, today Nene is standing here to show everyone the results of her usual lessons, so I want to move on to the next part soon!
みんなトレンド1位！え、早い！みんなありがとう！
Everyone, trending #1! Eh, so fast! Thank you everyone!
トレンド1位なんだって、みんな！
I'm trending #1, everyone!
わー、ねね、泣いちゃうよ。みんなありがとう。
Wow, Nene's going to cry. Thank you everyone.
みんな、ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much, everyone!
はい、というわけで早速次の曲行っていきたいと思います！それでは聴いてください、「最強パルパレード」！
Alright, so I'd like to go straight to the next song. Please listen to "Saikyou Palparade"!
最強パルパレード
Saikyou Palparade
作詞：畑亜貴/作曲：田代智一
Lyrics: Aki Hata / Composition: Tomokazu Tashiro
今や最強パレパレード
Now it's the strongest Pare-Parade
つまり最高ハッピーハッピー
Meaning, the ultimate happy-happy
みんな前進パレパレード
Everyone's moving forward, Pare-Parade
つまり更新ハッピーハッピー
Meaning, updating happy-happy
未来撃ち落とせよ
Shoot down the future
何もかもが虚ろなら
If everything is hollow
私たちが集まる必然性
The inevitability of our meeting
今を知れ
Know the now
誰も誰も気付かない
No one, no one notices
不思議秘密集めたら
If you collect wonder and secrets
異次元さえ微笑むのよ
Even other dimensions will smile
サンキュー叶えたいと ワンデイ願ったなら
Thank you. If I wished one day that I wanted it to come true
それは実に素晴らしく 思い通りブラボー
That would be truly wonderful. Bravo, just as I'd hoped.
ミステリー明日も今日も 分かんないから面白いわ
Mystery. Tomorrow and today... I don't know, so it's interesting.
いつでもお見通しなんて 退屈よ
Knowing everything all the time is boring.
どうして落ち込んでるの 冒険足りないんじゃない？
Why are you feeling down? Not enough adventure, maybe?
集まろうブラボー
Let's gather. Bravo!
野望に道が灯り
Ambition lights the path
今や最強パレパレード
Now it's the strongest Pare-Parade
つまり最高ハッピーハッピー
Meaning, the ultimate happy-happy
みんな享楽パレパレード
Everyone's enjoying the Pare-Parade
幕があるの当然よ
Of course there's a curtain call
レッツ・ぱちまったね
Let's patch matters!
1人1人違うから 私たちに関わりたくなくても痛くない
Since everyone is different, it doesn't hurt
even if you don't want to get involved with us.
恐る恐る近づいて 巻き込まれたなんてね
後から文句言わずするわよ
Approaching timidly, then claiming you were dragged in...
don't go complaining about it later.
三位 特別にはきっと理由があるのなら
それを探りましょう 弱気知らずのチャレンジ
Sunday, if there's surely a reason for being special,
let's find it. A challenge that knows no weakness.
ライ・ライ・人生なんて 想い変えられるのよ 今日をよ
Lie, lie, life can be changed by your thoughts...
today!
向き不向き 10度回れば違うし
Suitability or unsuitability...
turn just 10 degrees and things are different.
なんて考えすぎて 憂鬱抱えちゃうのさ やめようよ
希望はもっとクレイジー
Thinking too much like that makes you harbor gloom.
Let's stop it. Hope is even crazier.
夢は大胆にグレグレ たまに猛暑ヤバヤバ
Dreams are boldly 'gre-gre',
sometimes the heat is 'yaba-yaba'.
みんな天才ハレハレ 踊り決めてもう一回
Everyone is a genius 'hare-hare'.
Let's decide on a dance and do it one more time!
さあ 唱えよう
Now, let's chant!
三位 胸の中で ワット・デイ 誓ってみて
Sunday, in my heart, 'What day',
try swearing an oath.
それが実に素晴らしく 思い通りフラボー
That's truly wonderful, exactly as planned, bravo!
ミステリー 明日も今日も わかんないから面白いわ
いつでも お見通しなれたいんすよ
Mystery, tomorrow and today...
it's interesting because we don't know.
I want to be able to see through everything anytime.
ライ・ライ・人生なんて 想い変えられるのよ
集まろうよ 野望に満ちた物語
Lie, lie, life can be changed by your thoughts.
Let's gather together! A story full of ambition.
いまや最強パレ・パレ つまり最高ハッピー・ハッピー
Now it's the strongest 'Pare-Pare',
in other words, the ultimate happy-happy!
みんな狂乱パレ・パレ 文句あるの当然よ
Everyone is a frantic 'Pare-Pare'.
It's natural to have complaints!
夢は大胆にグレグレ たまに猛暑ヤバヤバ
Dreams are boldly 'gre-gre',
sometimes the heat is 'yaba-yaba'.
みんな天才ハレハレ 踊り決めてもう一回
Everyone is a genius 'hare-hare'.
Let's decide on a dance and do it one more time!
ありがとうございましたー！
Thank you so much!
最強パレパレード、お聞きいただきました。
どうだったでしょうか？
You just heard 'Saikyou Pare Parade'.
How was it?
はぁ〜、実はこの曲ね、あの、3D化決定する前に、
Phew... actually, regarding this song,
before the 3D was decided...
あ、それが発表される前に、メン限の方でね、
この曲やるんだけど、
or rather, before it was announced,
I told everyone in a members-only stream...
今、練習状況としてはこんな感じっていうのをね、
あの、みんなに放送でお伝えしてたんだよね。
that I'd be doing this song, and shared how
my practice was going back then.
そん時はね、とても、人に見せれるような
もんじゃなかったんだけど、
At that time, it really wasn't in a state
to show people, but...
ま、何とかここまで、何とかね、ここまで、
何とか、なりました。みんなありがとう。
somehow I made it here. Somehow...
I managed to get to this point. Thank you everyone.
ちょっとお水、失礼します。
Excuse me, I'm going to drink some water.
よいしょ。
Hup.
さてさてさてさて、みんな。どう、このステージ。
Now, now, now, everyone. How's this stage?
これね、お昼のステージなの。すごいでしょ。
もうめっちゃねね要素いっぱいの
This is the daytime stage. Amazing, right?
It's full of Nene elements...
ステージを作ってもらいました。遊園地なの。
スーパーねねちステージ。イェーイ！
I had them make this stage for me. It's an
amusement park. Super Nenechi Stage. Yay!
あとね、あのね、客席にね、根っ子の皆がいるんだよね。
ほら見て。
And also, the Nekkos are in the audience. Look!
すごい皆、同じ動きでペンライト振ってくれてる。
皆、コメントの皆、
Wow, everyone's waving their penlights with
the same movements. Everyone in the comments,
ここにいるんだ今日は。えーとね、今日はその
ステージにいる皆の中から、
you're all here today. So, today, from
among everyone on the stage,
こうね、何人か、ねねのステージ上に
上がってきてもらいたいと思いますので。
I'd like to have a few of you
come up onto Nene's stage.
それでは、え、根っ子の皆、どうぞステージへ！
So, Nekkos, please come to the stage!
どうぞステージへ！どうぞステージへ！
どうぞステージへ！
Please come to the stage! Please come to the stage!
Please come to the stage!
ニョインニョインって出てきたｗ
They popped out like "nyoin nyoin" lol.
ねぇ見て。あ、スカートの中見ないでｗ
見てって言ったの、私が間違えたわ。
Look. Ah, don't look under my skirt lol.
I'm the one who said "look", that was my mistake.
スカートの中見ないでね、皆。
Don't look under the skirt, okay everyone?
やだ、見ないでｗ 根っ子の皆、なんとこれ見て見て。
普段オレンジ色の人参の子だけなんだけど、
Stop it, don't look lol. Nekkos, look at this!
Usually it's just the orange carrot kids,
これ、なんと大根の子とごぼうの子も
一緒に作てもらいました！ありがとう！
but they also made radish kids and
burdock kids for me! Thank you!
素晴らしい、ありがとう！
Wonderful, thank you!
なんとね、この根っ子の皆、あ、ね、ほら見て見てこれ。
And you know, these Nekkos... ah, look at this.
ほら、地面に埋もれてる子達いるでしょこれ。
この子達ちょっと持ってみたいたいと思います。
Look, there are kids buried in the ground here.
I'd like to try picking them up.
はっ、よいしょーい！
Hup, heave-ho!
テテーン！ このねねのライブどうだった？
まだ二曲目なんだけどさ。
Ta-da! How was Nene's live?
It's only the second song, but...
もうねね汗びちょびちょなんだ、もう今。
Nene is already soaked in sweat right now.
えっ、良かったって？ うん、そっかそっか良かった。
Eh, it was good? I see, I see, that's good.
えーもう、すごい踊り狂いたい位こう、嬉しい気持ち...
I'm just so happy I want to dance like crazy...
みんなすごいでハッピーでいっぱいだって。
Everyone is amazing and full of happiness.
じゃあ、踊り狂ってもらうわ。
Well then, I'll have you dance like crazy.
はい、どうぞ！
Alright, go ahead!
ああ、いいぜ！
Ah, that's great!
もう一回！もう一回ちょっと踊り狂ってもらうわ。
One more time! I'll have you dance like crazy once more.
ちょっとうまく映んなかった。
It didn't show up very well.
行きます！
Here we go!
ほら、踊り狂えよ！
Come on, dance like crazy!
うん、いい感じ、いい感じだぁ。
Yeah, looking good, looking good.
えーっと、えーっと... じゃあ次はこの子！
Um, um... Well then, next is this one!
デデン！
Ta-da!
ごぼうの子！ねねのライブどうだった？
The Burdock boy! How was Nene's live?
最高だったよ！ありがとね、ねねちゃん。
It was the best! Thank you, Nene-chan.
俺たちにアイドルという夢を見させてくれてありがと！
Thank you for letting us dream of being idols!
あー、どういたしまして！
Oh, you're very welcome!
お利口さんだなぁ、本当によくできた子だ。
What a good boy, a really well-behaved child.
そして最後は... おいしょー！
And finally... heave-ho!
これ！いつものみんな！
This one! The usual everyone!
今日、新しいオープニングで瓶詰めされてたでしょ、みんな。
You were all bottled up in the new opening today, weren't you?
これ、いつものみんななの。
This is the usual everyone.
この子ね... 一人でプランプランするｗ
This one... hangs around by himself lol.
一人でプランプランするんだ、この子は。
This child just hangs around all on his own.
よいしょ。ほい。
Heave-ho. There.
ねー、かわいいねー。
Right? So cute.
かわいくくっついてもらっちゃって、みんな。
Having everyone stick to me so cutely.
よいしょ、よいしょ。
Heave-ho, heave-ho.
えー、じゃあここでね、ちょっとねねの全身をね、見てほしいので、
Well, now, I'd like you all to see Nene's full body,
はい、ねっ子のみんな！
Okay, Nenekko everyone!
ねっ子のみんなパンツ見えちゃうから、ほら、客席戻りなさい、みんな。
Nenekko, I can see your panties, so go back to your seats, everyone.
ほら、戻って戻って、みんな、はい。
Come on, back you go, everyone, okay.
あーすごい、一気に消えるじゃん、みんな。
Wow, you're all disappearing at once.
はい、というわけで、じゃあちょっとねねの全身をね、ゆっくり...
Okay, so, well, I'll show off Nene's full body slowly...
ゆっくり見てもらおうと思います！はい、カメラマンさんお願いします！
I want you to take a slow look! Okay, cameraman, please!
おー。
Ohh.
どう？どう？わらみ、ほら、はい。
How is it? How is it? Look, an armpit view.
わらみ、これ。
This is an armpit view.
どう？ｗｗｗ
How is it? lol
どう？みんなかわいい？助かるって？
How is it? Is it cute, everyone? Are you 'saved'?
ありがとー！
Thank you!
はい、はい、はい、かわいい。
Yes, yes, yes, cute.
あー、いいじゃん、いいじゃん！
Ah, looking good, looking good!
ありがとー！みんなすごいコメント爆速、助かる、ありがとー！
Thank you! Everyone's comments are super fast, thanks, thank you!
どう？こんなねねとか...
How's this? This kind of Nene...
こんなねねとか... いいんじゃないの？
Or this kind of Nene... isn't it nice?
あー、とってもいい感じだね！
Ah, feels very good!
よーし！じゃあここでね、みんなもノリノリになったところで、次の曲を聴いてもらおうかな。
Alright! Well then, now that everyone's in the groove, I'll have you listen to the next song.
次はね、この遊園地のね、お隣に桃の木がね、すっごいいっぱい咲いてるらしくて、
Next, apparently, right next to this amusement park, there are tons of peach trees in full bloom,
そっちに映って、移動... えーっと、歌をまた歌っていきたいと思いますので、
So I'll move over there... and I'd like to sing again, so...
それではみんな、昼の部はここまで！
Well then everyone, that's it for the afternoon session!
夕方の部へ、レッツ...
To the evening session, let's...
ゴゴゴゴゴゴゴゴゴゴゴゴゴゴ...
Go-go-go-go-go-go-go-go...
イェイ！
Yay!
恋☆カナ　ピタッときたナ　成功いかなえて
Koi☆Kana, it fits perfectly, make my success come true
奇跡的な　行ったり来たり　だって止まらないで
Miraculous, going back and forth, because it won't stop
いつか星を描いて　君へと届けたい
Drawing a star someday, I want to deliver it to you
一緒にいれるところが　夢心地の散歩道
The place where we can be together is a dreamy path for a walk
届きそうに見せるのが　イマドキの運命
Showing that it's within reach is today's destiny
甘いものほど沁みる胸の
Sweet things soak into the chest
隙間に君の照れた笑顔　まだ途中だけど
In the gap, your shy smiling face, although it's still in progress
ありがとう
Thank you
◎恋☆カナ
◎Koikana
イェイ！
Yay!
恋☆カナ ピタッときたら 正解！ 恋☆カナ 叶えて
Is it love? If it feels right, it's correct! Is it love? Make it come true
直感的な 行ったり来たり だって 止まんないって
Intuitive back and forth, because it won't stop
いつの日か 星になりたい 君の 二つ星
One day I want to be a star, your binary star
駆け引きの 彼女さえ 見当たらずにため息
Even the strategic girl is nowhere to be seen, and I sigh
なんて 姿を見せたって いいじゃないのね
It's okay to show such a side of myself, isn't it?
ドラマチックだと思われても
Even if it's thought to be dramatic
それ、それどころじゃないゲーム
That... it's no time for a game
けど どこまでも よろしくね
But forever more, please treat me well
イェイ！
Yay!
恋☆カナ キュンときたわ 痛い... この恋からだって
Is it love? It went 'kyun', it hurts... even from this love
絶妙的な すれ違いだって 気にしないで
Don't mind the exquisite near-misses
もっと 強く光るよ 胸の 一番星
I'll shine even brighter, the brightest star in my heart
雨の朝も 笑って見せて
Even on rainy mornings, show me a smile
星空を 期待でキラキラ
Starry sky, sparkling with expectation
レボリューションなんか 起こせなーい
I can't cause a revolution or anything
イェイ！
Yay!
恋☆カナ ピタッときたら 正解！ 恋☆カナ 叶えて
Is it love? If it feels right, it's correct! Is it love? Make it come true
決定的な ハッピーを呼ぼう すぐそこまで
Let's call for a definitive happy ending, it's just right there
願い切り 走って キラリ 流れ星
Running with all my wishes, a sparkling shooting star
恋☆カナ ピタッときたよ この恋 叶って
Is it love? It felt right, this love has come true
直感的な 行ったり来たり だって 迷わないで
Intuitive back and forth, so don't hesitate
いつの日か 星になりたい 君の 二つ星
One day I want to be a star, your binary star
ありがとうございましたー！
Thank you very much!
ただいまの曲は「恋☆カナ」という曲をお聴きいただきました。
Uh, the song you just heard was "Koikana."
皆に聴いてもらいました！
I had everyone listen to it!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
「恋☆カナ」はね、もうねねがすっごい、すっごい、すっごい、すっごい憧れてる...
"Koikana" is, well, Nene really, really, really, really admires...
アイドルの、きらりん☆レボリューションの月島きらりちゃんの代表曲を歌わせていただきました。
...the idol Tsukishima Kirari-chan from Kirarin Revolution, and I sang her signature song.
どうだった？この曲すっごい難しいの。
How was it? This song is really difficult.
さて、あのー、場所を移動してきて夕方のステージに来たんだけど...
Now then, um, I moved locations and came to this evening stage...
すごい、あのー、エモティックでしょ？
It's very, um, "emotic," right?
エモエモティックティックでしょ？
"Emo-emo-tic-tic," right?
今はとっても元気な曲を聴いてもらったんだけど...
You just listened to a very energetic song, but...
次はこの背景に合うようなすごいエモ目に皆に聴いてもらおうかなーと思って。
...next I thought I'd have you listen to something really "emo" that matches this background.
ただねねの息切れがちょっと収まらないから...
However, Nene's shortness of breath hasn't quite subsided...
エモさ...エモさよりもう、何ていうか、とっても...
The "emo-ness"... rather than emo-ness, more like, it's very...
あのー、息切れのほうが出ちゃうかもしれないけど、聴いてもらおう。
Um, my shortness of breath might come through more, but please listen.
ちょっと休憩もしちゃう。
I'll take a little break too.
よいしょ。すごくない？なんかこの光が...
Heave-ho. Isn't it amazing? Like, this light...
お水飲むのもなんかすごい様になっちゃうな。
Even drinking water looks so cool.
あー...
Ah...
綺麗な中で、ねねは一曲歌いたいと思います。
In this beautiful setting, Nene would like to sing a song.
それでは聴いてください。
Please listen to it.
ガーネット。
Garnet.
ガーネット / 作詞・作曲 奥華子
Garnet / Lyrics & Composition: Hanako Oku
グラウンド 駆けてく あなたの背中は
Your back as you run across the sports ground
空に浮かんだ 雲よりも自由で
Is freer than the clouds floating in the sky
ノートに並んだ 四角い文字さえ
Even the square letters lined up in my notebook
すべてを照らす 光に見えた
Seemed like light illuminating everything
この時間が その意味を私に
This time, its meaning to me...
教えてくれた
Has taught me
ガーネット
Garnet
あなたと過ごした日々を この胸に焼き付けよう
I'll etch the days I spent with you into my heart
思いださなくても 大丈夫なように
So that it'll be okay even if I don't remember them
いつか他の誰かを 好きになったとしても
Even if I fall in love with someone else someday
あなたは ずっと 特別で
You will always be special
大切で またこの季節が
And precious, and as this season
めぐってくる
Comes around again
初めて二人で 話した放課後
That time after school when we first spoke, just the two of us
誰も知らない 笑顔探していた
I was looking for a smile that no one else knew
遠くであなたの はしゃいでる声に
At the sound of your cheerful voice in the distance
なぜだか胸が 痛くなったの
For some reason, my chest started to ache
変わってゆくことを 怖がってたの
I was afraid of things changing
ずっと友達のまま いれる気がした
I felt like we could stay friends forever
終わってゆくものなど ないと思った
I thought there were no such things as things that end
果てしない時の中で あなたと出会えたことが
Meeting you in the midst of endless time
何よりも私を 強くしてくれたね
Strengthened me more than anything else
夢中でかける明日に たどり着いたとしても
Even if I reach the tomorrow I'm running toward so blindly
あなたは ずっと 特別で
You will always be special
大切で またこの季節が
And precious, and as this season
やってくる
Comes around
ぐるぐるしないでください お願いします
Please don't spin around. Please.
いつまでも 忘れないと
That you would never forget
あなたが言ってくれた夏
The summer you told me that
時が流れ 今頃私は
Time flows, and around now I
涙が こぼれてきた
Find tears overflowing
あなたと過ごした日々を この胸に焼き付けよう
I'll etch the days I spent with you into my heart
思いださなくても 大丈夫なように
So that it'll be okay even if I don't remember them
いつか他の誰かを 好きになったとしても
Even if I fall in love with someone else someday
あなたは ずっと 特別で
You will always be special
大切で またこの季節が
And precious, and as this season
めぐってくる
Comes around again
ありがとうございました！
Thank you so much!
えー、ガーネットお聞きいただきました。
Um, you just heard "Garnet."
ありがとうございました。
Thank you very much.
さあ、どうだったでしょうか。途中なんか「うわ、ぐるぐるしてる」ってみんなが言うからね、気になっちゃって気になっちゃってしょうがなかったけど
Now, how was it? In the middle, everyone was saying "Whoa, it's spinning," so I couldn't help but be really worried about it,
なんとか、なんとか耐えてる？ なんとか耐えてる。よかったよかった。
But somehow, is it somehow holding up? Somehow it's holding up. Good, good.
ふぅ、危ねえ危ねえ。
Phew, that was close, that was close.
ありがとね、みんな。
Thanks, everyone.
みんなの、あれじゃない？コメントがすごいあの、熱意を持ってるから、
Isn't it because of your comments? Because your comments are so passionate,
YouTubeとかがちょっと恥ずかしくなっちゃったんじゃないの？みんな。ありがとね。
Maybe YouTube and such got a little embarrassed? Everyone, thanks.
さてさて、夕方のステージだったんだけどね
Now then, it was an evening stage,
今日は、昼の部 夕方の部 そして、夜の部まであるんだよね、みんな！
But today, there's a daytime part, an evening part, and even a nighttime part, everyone!
というわけでね、夜の部に移動していきたいと思います！
So, I'm going to move on to the nighttime part!
夜の部へ、レッツラーゴー！
To the nighttime part, let's-a-go!
3, 2, 1, はい！
3, 2, 1, high!
Booo!
作詞・作曲:TOKOTOKO(西沢さんP)
Lyrics/Composition: TOKOTOKO (Nishizawasan-P)
ここからは2曲連続！
Next is two songs in a row!
また始まった 忘れん坊
It started again, being forgetful
手帳の隅っこだって カレンダーにだって丸しておいたのに
I even marked the corner of my notebook and the calendar
どうして怒ってるか 分かりますか？
Do you know why I'm angry?
謝っても許さないんだからね！
I won't forgive you even if you apologize!
もう知らない！
I don't care anymore!
どこにでもあるような
Like you'd find anywhere
どこにもないような
Like you'd find nowhere
幸せ探しはまだ始まったばっか
The search for happiness has only just begun
大事にしてたプリンだって
Even the pudding I was cherishing
君に食べられるために 生まれたわけじゃなかったのにな
Wasn't born just to be eaten by you, though...
それちょっとだけちょうだい
Give me just a little bit of that
ねぇ一口だけちょうだいなんて
Hey, saying things like "just one bite"
あまりにも都合良すぎませんか？
Isn't that just a bit too convenient?
吐いちゃったらいらない
If you spit it out, I don't want it
残しちゃったらごめんなさいって
If you leave some, saying "I'm sorry"
君のせいかしら
I wonder if it's your fault
言いたいぜったい 私のこと
I definitely want to say it, about me
どれくらい愛してるって 言葉じゃなくて形で示して
Tell me how much you love me, not with words, but with actions
今日がなんの日か忘れてた？
Did you forget what day it is today?
でも誕生日だって言うのも ちょっとね
But even saying it's my birthday is a bit...
もう嫌い！
I hate you!
合格するかしないとか
Whether you pass or not
子供だなんてほしいとか
Or wanting children and such
幸せ格好計画 駆け上げる前に
Before rushing into your "happiness-pose-plan"
たまにはお酒を控えるとか
Like refraining from alcohol occasionally
明日から真面目にやるとか
Or saying you'll take things seriously from tomorrow
だらだら付いてる チャチャチャチャチャチャン
Trailing along lazily, cha-cha-cha-cha-cha-chan
それちょっとだけちょうだい
Give me just a little bit of that
ねぇ一口だけちょうだいなんて
Hey, saying things like "just one bite"
あまりにも都合良すぎませんか？
Isn't that just a bit too convenient?
吐いちゃったらいらない
If you spit it out, I don't want it
残しちゃったらごめんなさいって
If you leave some, saying "I'm sorry"
君のせいかしら
I wonder if it's your fault
一口だけちょうだい
Give me just one bite
もう一口だけちょうだいなんて
Saying things like "just one more bite"
甘え上手で 罪なんじゃないの？
Aren't you quite the sweet-talker? It's almost a sin
ちょっとだけちょうだい
Give me just a little bit
ねぇできたら全部ちょうだいなんて
Hey, saying things like "give me it all if you can"
君のせいかしら
I wonder if it's your fault
私のせいかしら
I wonder if it's my fault
やっと君のせいかしら
Finally, I wonder if it's your fault
おしまい！
The end!
限られた時の中で
Within the limited time
どれだけのことができるの
How much can we do?
言葉にならないほどの
To the point words can't describe
Story
作詞/作曲: 2SOUL
Lyrics/Composition: 2SOUL
そうだろう
Is that so
言葉にならないほどの想いを
The feelings that are beyond words
どれだけあなたに伝えられるだろう
How much of it can I convey to you
ずっと閉じ込めてた
I had been keeping them locked up
胸の痛みを消してくれた
You took away the pain in my heart
今私が笑えるのは
The reason why I can smile now
一緒に泣いてくれた君がいたから
Is because you were there to cry with me
一人じゃないから
Because I'm not alone
君が私を守るから
Because you protect me
強くなれる もう何も怖くないよ
I can be strong, I'm not afraid of anything anymore
時がなだめてく
Time will soothe it
痛みと共に流れてく
It will flow away along with the pain
日の光が優しく照らしてくれる
The sunlight shines gently on me
説明することや
There's no need to explain
無理して笑うことも しなくていいから
Or to force a smile anymore
何かあるなら
If there's something wrong
いつでも頼ってほしい
I want you to rely on me anytime
疲れた時は肩を貸すから
I'll lend you my shoulder when you're tired
どんなに強がっても
No matter how much you try to be strong
ため息くらいするときもある
There are times when you sigh
孤独じゃない 扉を
You're not alone, the door...
共に立ち上がればまた
If we stand up together again
動き始める
It will start moving
一人じゃないから
Because you're not alone
私が君を守るから
Because I will protect you
あなたの笑う顔が見たいと思うから
Because I want to see your smiling face
時がなだめてく
Time will soothe it
痛みと共に流れてく
It will flow away along with the pain
日の光が優しく照らしてくれる
The sunlight shines gently on me
時に人は傷つき
Sometimes people get hurt
傷つけながら
And hurt others
染まる日はそれぞれ違うけど
The days we are colored are different
自分だけのストーリー
Your very own story
作りながら生きていくのだから
Since we live while creating it
ずっと ずっと
Always, always
諦めないで
Please don't give up
一人じゃないから
Because you're not alone
私が君を守るから
Because I will protect you
あなたの笑う顔が見たいと思うから
Because I want to see your smiling face
時がなだめてく
Time will soothe it
痛みと共に流れてく
It will flow away along with the pain
日の光が優しく照らしてくれる
The sunlight shines gently on me
ありがとうございましたー！
Thank you very much!
えー、『Aipho』と『Story』の
Well, you just listened to
2曲をお聴きいただきました。イエーイ！
'Aipho' and 'Story'. Yay!
よいしょ。ちょっとお水飲ませてください。ありがとうございました。
Alright. Let me drink some water. Thank you.
おい... ちょっと夜に水飲むのもなかなかエモいな。
Oh... Drinking water at night is quite emotional.
よいしょ。さて、あの、クマのねねちじゃなくなったところで、
Alright. Now that I'm no longer Bear Nenechi,
ちょっとね、もう一回、ちょっとみんなにスクショを、スクショを撮ってもらいたくて、
I'd like everyone to take some screenshots, some screenshots,
お写真いっぱい撮っちゃって、みんな。よいしょ。
Take lots of photos, everyone. Alright.
ね、どういう感じがみんな好み？
Hey, what kind of (poses) does everyone like?
あーいいね。ちょっとコメントにさ、
Ah, nice. Could you maybe in the comments,
リクエストさ、してくれない？
give me some requests?
こういうのとかある？
Something like this?
あ、こういうのとかある？
Oh, how about something like this?
おい、いいじゃん、
Hey, not bad,
お強そうだね。
looks strong, doesn't it?
あ、いいね。
Ah, nice.
いいっす。
It's good.
あ、いい。
Ah, good.
いいじゃん、いいじゃん。
Not bad, not bad.
可愛いポーズしてって。
Do a cute pose, they say.
可愛いポーズってなんだ？
What's a "cute pose"?
お、わー、いい、
Oh, wow, good,
あ、ああ、いいっすね。
oh, ah, that's nice.
ローアングルめちゃくちゃいいじゃん。
The low angle is great.
あーいい、ローアングルめっちゃいいの。
Ah, good, the low angle is really good.
あーいいね、いい。
Ah, nice, good.
ねねねねねねやってたポーズ。
The pose I did in my "Nenenenene".
え、なんだろう、これ？
Um, what was it, this?
ウッキー！
Ukki!
お猿さんみたいなポーズとか。
Like a monkey pose.
これとか。
Like this.
これすごいあれ、お気に入りなの。
I really like this one.
シャキーン！
Shakiin!
おい、いいじゃん、いいじゃん。
Hey, not bad, not bad.
あのさ、ちょっとさ、アップでさ、
Um, hey, in a close-up,
アップでさ、
in a close-up,
あのキラキラのお目目のやつに変えるからさ、
I'm gonna change to the sparkly eyes version,
ちょっとみんな見てて。
so everyone watch.
いくよ。
Here I go.
キラキラお目目！
Sparkly eyes!
んーはっ！
Mmm-ha!
え、どう？
How is it?
いい感じ？
Looking good?
イェーイ！
Yay!
イェイ、イェイ、イェイ、イェイ、イェーイ！
Yay, yay, yay, yay, yay!
あ、いいじゃん。
Ah, not bad.
あーいいじゃん。
Ah, nice.
ありがとう。
Thank you.
撮った？
Did you take photos?
みんな、撮ってくれた？
Everyone, did you take them for me?
えー、いい感じ。
Eh, looking good.
いい、いい。
Good, good.
え、いい。
Eh, good.
ちょっと、もうちょっと、なんか、お...
A bit, a little more, like, oh...
なんかいいアングルないかな。
Is there a good angle?
みんなちょっと撮って。
Everyone, please take some photos.
これ撮ってさ、あの、ツイートして。
Take this and, you know, tweet it.
ねね貰うじゃん、後から。
I'll pick them up later.
あ、この後ろのさ、背景と入る感じ。
Ah, this background behind me, the way it fits in.
おーめっちゃいいな。
Oh, that's really nice.
あーいいね。
Ah, nice.
みんなめっちゃいいじゃん。
Everyone, that's really great.
え、ちょっとこっちからさ、なんだろうな、
Eh, from over here, let's see,
ステージ全体をこう、映す感じの。
like, showing the entire stage.
あー、いい！
Ah, good!
あ、いい！
お、おおー、すごくない？
Oh, ooh, isn't this amazing?
めっちゃいい。
It's really good.
みんな、ねねだよ！
Everyone, it's Nene!
あー、めっちゃよくない、これ？
Ah, isn't this really good?
いい。
Good.
ウィンクして、
Wink for me,
ウィンク。
wink.
ウィンクか。
A wink?
よし、いくぞ。
Okay, here I go.
はっ、はっ！
Ha, ha!
あ、いい。
Ah, good.
いい。
Good.
えー、いいじゃん！
Eh, not bad!
カメラマンさんが忙しくて大変そうって？
You say the cameraman seems busy and having a hard time?
大変ですか？
Are you having a hard time?
「全然」って言ってたよ、
He said "not at all",
今、みんな。
just now, everyone.
一番！
Number one!
あ、いい。
Ah, good.
これいい。
This is good.
あ、これ後ろ姿でさ、
Ah, I want this from behind,
客席でさ、欲しいな。
with the audience.
あ、やった。
Ah, I did it.
あ、よくない？
Ah, isn't this good?
おー、よくない？
Oh, isn't it good?
おー、めっちゃよくない？
Oh, isn't it really good?
めっちゃよくない？
Isn't it really good?
は、はっ、あ、みんなこれ、
Ha, ha, ah, everyone, this is
ライブでよくあるやつじゃん。
that thing you often see at live concerts.
写真撮ろう、
Let's take a photo,
みんな写真。
everyone, a photo.
ちょっとしゃがんでいいですか？
Can I crouch down a bit?
はっ！
Ha!
あ、ライブっぽい！
Ah, it feels like a live concert!
ライブっぽい！
Like a live concert!
みんな、パシャパシャ撮って、
Everyone, snap-snap away,
パシャパシャ。
snap-snap.
はい、もう一パターン。
Okay, another pattern.
はい。
Here.
はい、
Yes,
yes,
はい。
yes.
えー、めちゃめちゃいい。
Eh, it's really good.
え、待って、これいいな。
Eh, wait, this is nice.
わー、わー、めちゃめちゃいいじゃん。
Wow, wow, it's really good.
ちょっと、めっちゃいいの撮れた。
Man, I got a really good one.
おー、最高じゃん、これみんな。
Oh, it's the best, this is, everyone.
ナイス。
Nice.
ナイス、ナイス。
Nice, nice.
さてさて、じゃ、ねね、次、第、曲の説明しちゃおうかな、
Well then, well, Nene will explain the next song,
そろそろ。
soon.
あ、いいよ、まだ撮ってていいからね。
Ah, it's okay, you can keep taking photos.
この感じで説明しようか、次の曲まで。
Shall I explain like this until the next song?
どういうのがいいかな。
What would be good?
あ、これで説明するわ、じゃ。
Ah, I'll explain with this, then.
えー、次の曲はですね、
Um, the next song,
あの、みんなからすごくリクエストが多かったんですけど。
well, I've had so many requests for it from everyone.
あの、なかなかね、あの、歌枠とかでは歌わずに、
Well, I haven't really sung it in my karaoke streams or anything,
今までずっと取っておいた曲をね、
I've been saving it until now,
披露していきたいと思うんですよ、皆さん。
and I'd like to perform it for you all, everyone.
お披露目していきたいと思います。
I'd like to perform it.
この曲もね、踊りの振り付けがついておりますので、
This song also has dance choreography,
よかったら皆さん、え、ご賞味ください。
so please enjoy it if you'd like, everyone.
ご賞味ください？
Please "savor" it?
なんか、いい感じに見てもらうのってなんて言うんだっけな。
What was that phrase for having people watch it nicely?
皆さんご賞味ください。
Everyone, please savor it.
よろしくお願いします。
Thank you.
というわけで、
With that,
次の曲にいってみましょう。
let's move on to the next song.
それでは聴いてください。
Please listen to:
ファンサ。
Fansa.
好きになって　もっと
Like me more, more
私を見て　もっと
Look at me more, more
恩返しは　愛のこもった
My repayment is a love-filled
投げキッスで
blown kiss
気のせいじゃない
It's not your imagination
目は合ってるよ
our eyes are meeting
ハート作って
Make a heart
恋しちゃってください
and please fall in love
やれること
Anything I can do,
何でもします
I'll do it all
NG無しで
With no NGs,
体当たり挑戦
a full-body challenge
SNSで見つけたあっちの子
The girl I found on social media
不遇な誰よりわかってるし
I understand better than anyone unfortunate
でも大丈夫　ここに立てば
But it's okay, if I stand here
みんながいる
everyone is here
行くよ！
Here I go!
好きになって　もっと
Like me more, more
私を見て　もっと
Look at me more, more
恩返しは　愛のこもった
My repayment is a love-filled
投げキッスで
blown kiss
虜にする　もっと
I'll captivate you more, more
夢を見せる　もっと
I'll show you more dreams, more
楽しんでて　愛のこもった
Have fun, it's a love-filled
スペシャルナイト
special night
ファンサしちゃうぞ
I'm gonna give you fan service
お手紙も　書いてください
Please write me letters too
何度も読んで
I'll read them over and over
宝物にします
and make them my treasure
スキャンダル　まだ早いけど
Scandals, it's still too early
裏切りません
I won't betray you,
宣言しときます
I'll declare it now
嫉妬嫌がらせには負けない
I won't lose to jealousy or harassment
不遇な実力で勝ってやる
I'll win with my unfortunate skill
だからやめない　負けず嫌い
So I won't stop, I'm a sore loser
私はいる
I am here
行くよ！
Here I go!
拳上げて　もっと
Raise your fists more, more
汗をかいて　もっと
Sweat more, more
恩返しは　愛のこもった
My repayment is a love-filled
ねねビームで
Nene Beam
大歓声　もっと
Great cheers more, more
まだまだねぇ　もっと
Still more, hey, more
受け止めてね　愛のこもった
Please accept my love-filled
ワガママを
selfishness
ファンサしちゃうぞ
I'm gonna give you fan service
終わりの時間が近づく　寂しいね
The end is approaching, it's lonely, isn't it?
楽しいのに　泣きそうだよ
Even though it's fun, I feel like crying
次も　次も　また会えるよね
Next time, and the next, we can meet again, right?
約束！
Promise!
優しさに溢れている言葉
Words overflowing with kindness
心無い誰かの言葉さえ
Even the words of someone heartless
必要なんだ　必要なんだ
They're necessary, they're necessary,
強くなろう
let's become strong
好き叫んで　もっと
Shout your love more, more
楽しんじゃえ　もっと
Have fun more, more
忘れないで
Don't forget,
特別な日になりますように
I hope it becomes a special day
共に歌おう　ずっと
Let's sing together forever,
共に歩もう　ずっと
let's walk together forever,
合言葉は
The password is
とびきりのLOVE
a superb LOVE
好きになって　もっと
Like me more, more
私を見て　もっと
Look at me more, more
恩返しは　愛のこもった
My repayment is a love-filled
投げキッスで
blown kiss
虜にする　もっと
I'll captivate you more, more
夢を見せる　もっと
I'll show you more dreams, more
楽しんでて　愛のこもった
Have fun, it's a love-filled
スペシャルナイト
special night
ファンサしちゃうぞ
I'm gonna give you fan service
ありがとうございましたー！
Thank you very much!
えー、ファンサ、お聴きいただきましたー！
You've just heard "Fansa"!
ふぅ...みんな、どうだったでしょうか...
Whew... Everyone, how was it?
BGMくださーい！
BGM, please!
ふぁー、水...おいしょ...
Phew, water... heave-ho...
さてさて、もう8時も50分を迎えようとしております皆様。
Well then, everyone, it's already approaching 8:50.
今日ね、ここ、このためにね、ねねはずっと踊りとね、
You know, for today, for this, Nene has been
踊りながら歌うっていうことをね、練習してきたんだけど、
practicing dancing and singing while dancing,
その...
and...
みんなに見せられたぜ。
I got to show it to everyone.
どうだった、みんな？
What did you think, everyone?
どう、どう？
How was it? How was it?
あ、すごい、がんばった。
Ah, look at them working so hard.
あ、すごい良かった。
Ah, that was great.
うわあ、良かったか、良かった。
Whoa, was it good? I'm glad it was good.
がんばった甲斐があった、みんなありがとう。
It was worth the effort. Thank you, everyone.
ありがとな、まい…
Thanks, my...
というわけで、ここからはね、ねねから
And so, from here on, from Nene,
2点お知らせというか、重大発表というかがあります！
I have two announcements, or rather, huge announcements!
というわけで、1つ目の重大発表！ドーン！
So, here's the first major announcement! Ta-da!
桃鈴ねね 3D化記念グッズ 発売決定！
Momosuzu Nene 3D Debut Commemorative Goods are coming out!
桃鈴ねね 3D化記念グッズ
4月18日販売開始
Momosuzu Nene 3D Debut Commemorative Goods
On sale from April 18th
イェーイ！
Yay!
はい、というわけで、3Dのアクリルスタンドと、
Yes, so there's a 3D acrylic stand,
ねっこのラバーストラップと、
a Nekko rubber strap,
あとね、ねねがいつも着てる上着のあの胸元についてる、あのワッペンバッジが出ます！
and the wappen badge that's always on the chest of Nene's jacket!
というわけで、詳細を見ていきたいと思います。
So, let's take a look at the details.
1つ目、よいしょっ、えいっ！
First one... here we go, hup!
見て！3Dアクリルスタンド見て！
Look! Look at the 3D acrylic stand!
3Dアクリルスタンド
3D Acrylic Stand
わあ、めちゃめちゃめちゃめちゃ可愛い。
Whoa, it's super, super, super, super cute.
こんな感じ。
It looks like this.
え、こういう感じ。ああ、めっちゃいい感じでしょう、すごいね。
Yeah, like this. Ah, it looks great, doesn't it? Amazing.
可愛くお写真撮ってもらえたんだ。
I was able to get some cute photos taken.
この台座も見てよ、これ、立てるやつ。
Look at the base too, the thing that makes it stand.
すごいすごい可愛くない？
Isn't it super, super cute?
あのね、もう5期生みんなのあるから、その隣にね、
The other 5th Gen members have theirs too, so right next to them,
その隣にぜひ置いてもらって、なんだったらもう歴代先輩のみんなのあるからさ、
please place it right there. Or even next to your collection of seniors!
そこの隣に置いてもらって、よろしくお願いします。
Please put me right next to them. Thank you.
そしてもう1つの詳細、こちら！
And here are the other details!
ねっこのラバーストラップとHAANのね、ワッペンバッジなんだけど、
The Nekko rubber strap and the HAAN wappen badge.
「ねっ子」ラバーストラップ & 「HAAN」ワッペンバッジ
Nekko Rubber Strap & HAAN Wappen Badge
みんな見て、ねっこのラバーストラップ、ねねが描いたやつそのままラバーストラップにしてもらいました！
Look, everyone. For the Nekko rubber strap, they turned my drawing directly into a strap!
すっごい可愛い。
It's so cute.
わあ、もうめちゃめちゃ可愛い。見て、裏面にはねねのサインが入ってるんだよ、みんな、すごっ！
Whoa, it's just so cute. Look, it has Nene's signature on the back! Isn't that amazing?
すごくない、すごくない、すごくない？
Isn't it amazing? Isn't it amazing?
そしてね、HAANのね、ワッペンバッジなんだけど、これ見本の画像だからね、
And then, the HAAN wappen badge. This is just a sample image,
質感とかがちょっとあれなんだけどね、
so the texture might look a bit different,
あと本当にはワッペン、あの、めっちゃ布って感じ。
but the actual wappen feels really like fabric.
めっちゃ布って感じでね、裏面にあのバッジがついてて、
It feels very much like fabric, and it has a badge pin on the back,
だからね、5期生ってパーカー出してるんだよね。
so, you know, Gen 5 released hoodies.
5期生でパーカー出してるんだよね、みんな。だからそのパーカーにこうやってペチョッ！
Everyone in Gen 5 has a hoodie out. So you can stick it on that hoodie like this!
ぺぺぺぺぺチョッて貼るのどうだい、みんな？
How about sticking it on there, everyone?
ねねはお勧め、それがとってもお勧めだと思った。
Nene recommends it. I thought it would be a great idea.
はい、で、このグッズなんですけど、えっと、この後21時からね、え、販売開始になりますので、
So, these goods will be on sale starting from 21:00 today.
たぶん今概要欄が更新されたと思わーれるーので、
The description should have been updated by now, I think,
よかったらみんなそこからリンクどーんと飛んでもらって、あの、どう、みんな、お願い！
so please click the link there and check them out. Please, everyone!
お願い！お願い！
Please! Please!
ねねが喜ぶからみんなお願い、お願いお願いというわけでね、よかったらチェックしてください。
It would make Nene so happy, so please. Please check them out.
よろしくお願いします。
Thank you very much.
さて、もう1個の重大発表、みんななんだと思うかな、みんな。
Now, what do you think the other major announcement is?
なんだと思う？なんだと思う？
What do you think? What do you think?
はい、こちら！
Here it is!
桃鈴ねね 2ndシングル Lunch with me が、
Momosuzu Nene's 2nd single, 'Lunch with me',
桃鈴ねね 2ndシングル
Lunch with me
Momosuzu Nene 2nd Single
え、4月の19日0時から配信開始になります！
will be available starting from midnight on April 19th!
イェーイ！
Yay!
これね、なんと1曲目に続いて、ヒゲドライバー様、またお願い申し上げました。ありがとうございます！
For this one, following the first song, I asked Higedriver-sama again. Thank you so much!
えっとね、そう、最近忙しくてなかなかできなかったあの、お昼枠？
Well, you know, the lunch stream I haven't been able to do lately because I've been busy?
それに関する、え、曲が出ます！
A song about that is coming out!
ね、今回もねねがちゃんとジャケット描いてるので、よかったらね、チェックよろしくお願いします！
And Nene drew the cover art this time too, so please check it out!
さて、Lunch with me、一体どんな曲なんじゃろか。
Now, I wonder what kind of song 'Lunch with me' is.
気になるんじゃないんじゃろか！
I bet you're curious, aren't you!
というわけでですね、今日はね、みんなに生歌でLunch with meをね、ここで初披露しようと思ったんですけど、
So, I thought about doing the first live performance of 'Lunch with me' here today,
ちょっとね、この曲がね、もう出来立てほやほやすぎて、なかなかちょっとね、生歌練習する時間がなくて、
but this song is just so brand new that I didn't have much time to practice singing it live,
あ、でもどうせだったらみんなにすごい良いものを聞いてほしい。
but I really want you all to hear the best version of it.
と思ったねねは、ひらめいた。
So Nene had an idea.
完成音源聞いてもらおうと思って！
I'll let you hear the studio recording!
だからね、あの振り付けもまだないので、ねねが今からまあ大体こんな感じが可愛いんじゃないかなーって
So, I don't have the choreography yet, so I'll just move in a way I think is cute,
思った動きをしながら完成音源を聞いてもらいたいと思います！えー、
while you listen to the recording! Um...
今日は長い間見てくれてありがとうございました。
Thank you for watching for such a long time today.
なんと世界の、世界トレンドも、世界トレンドランキング、世界のトレンド1位も！ありがとうございます！
And we hit #1 on the worldwide trends! Thank you so much!
みんなすごい嬉しい、本当にありがとうみんな。
I'm so happy. Thank you so much, everyone.
今日のためにねねはいろんなこと頑張ってきたからね、ありがとう。
Nene worked hard on many things for today. Thank you.
今日はね、このLunch with meでラストの曲となってしまいますが、
This 'Lunch with me' will be the last song of the day,
...に慣れたね。ね、これからもいろんな、いろんなことができるように、
...I've gotten used to it. Right, so that I can do various, various things from now on,
頑張って、頑張って、頑張りたいと思っておりますので、
I want to work hard, work hard, and do my best,
これからも応援をよろしくお願いします！
so please continue to support me!
えー、直前に遊びに来てくれたラミィも、Discordをくれたみんなも、
Umm, Lamy, who came to visit just before, and everyone who messaged on Discord,
Twitterで反応してくれた先輩たちも、本当に本当にありがとうございました！
and the seniors who reacted on Twitter, thank you all so, so much!
わためも来てくれてありがとうございました！
Watame, thank you for coming as well!
本当に最高の日になってよかった。大雨警報だったらしいんだけど、
I'm so glad it turned out to be the best day. Apparently there was a heavy rain warning,
ピカピカに晴れたし！
but it cleared up perfectly!
本当に今日は最高の日でした。みんな本当にありがとう。
Today was truly the best day. Thank you everyone, really.
これからもねねのこと、よろしくお願いします！
Please keep supporting Nene!
というわけで、最後の曲、聴いてください！
And with that, please listen to the final song!
「Lunch with me」なんですけど、
It's "Lunch with me", but...
ちょっとごめんね、間違えちゃった、MCを今。
Wait, sorry, I messed up the MCing just now.
あのね、あのね、ここ夜じゃんか。
You see, you see, it's night here, right?
夜で「Lunch with me」ってなんかちょっとあれじゃない？
Isn't "Lunch with me" at night a bit... you know?
だからさ、今からねねの力でさ、
So, using Nene's power...
昼にさ、戻すからさ、昼のステージでねね、やっていい？
...I'll change it back to daytime. Can I perform on a daytime stage?
というわけで、お昼に戻れーー！
So, return to daytime!
昼！
Daytime!
昼に戻ってきたので、本当に最後の最後、聴いてください。
Since it's back to daytime, for the very last song, please listen.
Lunch with me!
Lunch with me
作詞・作曲 ヒゲドライバー
Lyrics & Composition: Hige Driver
遅く起きた朝は
On mornings when I wake up late
なんだかいつもより眠くて
I feel somewhat sleepier than usual
昨日の夜ずっと
Last night, I was...
漫画を読んでたから眠れなくてさ
reading manga all night and couldn't sleep
今頃そっちは
Right now, over there where you are...
どこで何してるかななんて
I wonder where you are and what you're doing
考えてたら心が
While thinking about that, my heart...
ふわっと軽くなるんだ
starts to feel light and airy
これは内緒なんだけど
This is a secret, but...
昨日読んだ漫画の
in the manga I read yesterday...
主人公に君がちょっと似てたんだよ
the protagonist looked a bit like you
ねえ お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 一緒に食べよう
Hey, lunch, lunch, lunch, lunch, lunch, lunch, let's eat together
ちょっとだけ同じ気持ち 共有したくて
I want to share the same feeling for just a bit
そう お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 だけでも
Yeah, lunch, lunch, lunch, lunch, lunch, lunch, even just that
特別なことじゃなくても
even if it's nothing special
いつもの君でいいんだよ
you can just be your usual self
一緒に食べよう
Let's eat together
照れ屋な『ずっと』は 言えない地味な日々だけど
A shy "forever" is something I can't say in these plain days, but...
なぜだろう最近は
I wonder why, but lately...
少しキラキラなんだ
it's a little sparkly
ほんの一分直前に
Just one minute before...
嫌なことあっても
even if something bad happened...
君に会えると思うと にやけちゃってさ
thinking about meeting you makes me grin
ねえ お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 一緒に食べよう
Hey, lunch, lunch, lunch, lunch, lunch, lunch, let's eat together
一人よりきっと 楽しくなるから
it'll surely be more fun than being alone
そう お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 だけだし
Yeah, lunch, lunch, lunch, lunch, lunch, lunch, it's just that
照れくさいようなことないから
so there's no need to feel embarrassed
変なこと考えないでよ
don't think about weird things
前向きに、けど
looking forward, though
知ってるかな
I wonder if you know
君がくれる
that what you give me...
言葉一つ一つ
every single word...
嬉しくなったり 楽しくなったり
makes me happy, makes me have fun
不思議なパワーを感じるってこと
that I feel a mysterious power
ねえ お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 一緒に食べよう
Hey, lunch, lunch, lunch, lunch, lunch, lunch, let's eat together
ちょっとだけ同じ気持ち 共有したくて
I want to share the same feeling for just a bit
そう お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼
Yeah, lunch, lunch, lunch, lunch, lunch, lunch...
...な奇跡でも
...even a miracle,
特別なことじゃなくても
Even if it's nothing special,
いつでも君がいいんだよ
It's always you that I want.
一緒に食べよう！
Let's eat together!
桃鈴ねね 3Dお披露目
Momosuzu Nene 3D Reveal
#桃鈴ねね3D
#MomosuzuNene3D